Hello! I am

Muh Syaiful Adli

Web Developer

CV Muh Syaiful Adli



ABOUT ME

I am a hard worker and a persistent learner. 2 years experience in website development at Yayasan Satu Karsa Karya. Always want to develop and learn the latest programming languages. Have good communication, analysis and problem solving skills.







PERSONAL INFORMATION

+62853-2525-5626

syaiful.adly2@gmail.com

Perumahan Demalika Sanggrahan 2 No A9, Sanggrahan, Grogol, Sukoharjo, Jawa Tengah

November 26th, 1995

FORMAL EDUCATION

2010 - 2013 SMA Negeri 4 Surakarta

2013 - 2018 Ilmu dan Teknologi Pangan Universitas Sebelas Maret Surakarta, GPA = 3.50

NON FORMAL EDUCATION

2021 HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and MySQL Course by Progate

2022 UI/UX Design Mastery Course by Skilvul

2022 React Developer Course by Teknoblox

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2020 Part-Time Teacher at Neo Evolution

2020 - 2021 Staff of Pengelolaan Data dan informasi Division at Yayasan Satu Karsa Karya

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

2015 Head of Kaderisasi Division at Kelompok Studi Ilmiah

2016 Head of Media Informasi Division at Kelompok Studi Ilmiah

Skills

Here are some programming languages that I have learned

